ioufreebies.com 2012-12-18

# Privacy Policy

IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons strictly adheres to the Privacy Policy outlined below. 

We will closely guard any personally identifiable information you disclose to us during registration or at any other point during your IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons.com experience. Information will only be shared with a third party if a member requests for that information to be shared. A member may request that this information be shared, by opting in to programs, lists or newsletters or participating in certain offers or promotions that may require information such as, but not be limited toe, first name, last name, occupation, email address, mailing address, phone number, selected interests or date of birth. Not all offers/programs/lists/opt-ins specify exactly which pieces of information will be shared. Please contact IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons through privacy@IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons if you would like more information about which offers/programs/lists/opt-ins require certain pieces of information to be shared. 

By joining IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons, you are opting-in to receive mail from IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons. You can unsubscribe from our list at any time and still maintain an active IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons account. 

**Information Collection and Use**

IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons collects information from our users at several different points on our Website. 

**Registration**

There is no registration requied in order to use this Website, A user is not required to give their contact information (such as name, email address and postal address). 

**Unsubscribe Requests**

If a member wishes to opt out of or unsubscribe their IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons account, they may use the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any email message. Every email contains a physical address to which a user can mail an unsubscribe request. Members may also send an unsubscribe request to our online privacy department at privacy@IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons at any time and a representative will opt that member out of our list within 3 days 

**Personal Information**

We currently do not collect any user information other than email address to sign up for our IOUFreebies newsletter. We will update our policy if we begin to collect sensitive user information. 

**Our Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data we store on the user's hard drive containing information about the user's account and point earnings. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. There are two reasons for the use of cookies on our site. The first reason is that it helps us keep track of the points you earn during a given session. The second reason for using cookies on our site is that it allows you to move throughout our site and complete offers without being prompted by our security system to log in again after each activity. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site, however they will have to log on multiple times and they risk not receiving credit for the points they have earned. 

**Log Files**

We do track certain information such as type of browser and log-on time for our own use, as well as Internet IP address. We use this information only to track where our users may be coming from and what type of software they are using. We keep this information so we can continuously improve our users' online experience and improve the IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons Website. None of this information is ever used to trace back to any specific person and is useful only to IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons. 

**Links to Other Sites**

This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons Website. IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons requests that users report any and all concerns about our partners' privacy practices directly to us at privacy@IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons. 

**Security**

This Website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit information via the Website, your information is protected both online and offline. While we use both passwords and user names to protect information online, we also do everything in our power to protect users' information offline. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our Member Support team) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access to your information. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment and professionally maintained. If you have any questions about the security at our Website, you can send a request to privacy@IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons 

**Special Offers and Email**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify their email address. We also require a new user to click on a link inserted in the initial email to verify their account. IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons does this in order to establish that the email address given upon registration is not fraudulent. Established members will occasionally receive emails containing information regarding new offers or special promotions from IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons or its partners if they have not opted out. "Opting-out" means the user does not wish to receive emails from IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons.com. When a member receives an email from IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons.com and decides they no longer wish to receive emails or want to be removed from our system, they can open the email and scroll to the bottom. At the bottom of the email page there will be a brief description of how to have an account "opted out". Once we receive information regarding these account changes, we will make the specified changes as soon as possible. Please note that while IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons can remove you from internal lists, if you have agreed to have your email transmitted to a third party through our site in the past, removal from that list is not guaranteed. 

**Site and Service Announcements**

Under rare circumstances, IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons may need to contact specific or all users in order to make important announcements about the IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons site or service changes. Members are not able to unsubscribe, or opt out of these announcements, because they may contain very important information regarding their accounts. Before these measures are taken, however, IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons will post information regarding changes directly on the Website. IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons reserves the right to contact users to correct account errors or to supply important information IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons deems relevant. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons users are able to change their personal information at any time. Members must request this information be changed, along with a valid reason for the change. If there are any questions, users may contact our team. 

Should you wish to contact us you can send email to: 

contact@ioufreebies.com. 

Physical mail may be sent to: 

IOUFreebies.com - Free Samples and Coupons  
1949 Route 70 East   
Suite 7   
Cherry Hill, NJ 08003 

Effective Date: December 1st, 2009
